Guide to the Steven Mallory White Papers, 1871-1901
Department of Special Collections
- Series 1. Correspondence
  - Subseries 2. Incoming
    - Richardson - Seymour (Box 35, Folder 379)
    - Shackleford - Stewart (Box 36, Folder 380)
    - Shackleford - Stewart (Box 36, Folder 381)
    - Shackleford - Stewart (Box 36, Folder 382)
    - Shackleford - Stewart (Box 36, Folder 383)
    - Shackleford - Stewart (Box 36, Folder 384)
    - Shackleford - Stewart (Box 36, Folder 385)
    - Shackleford - Stewart (Box 36, Folder 386)
    - Shackleford - Stewart (Box 36, Folder 387)
    - Shackleford - Stewart (Box 36, Folder 388)
    - Shackleford - Stewart (Box 36, Folder 389)
    - Shackleford - Stewart (Box 36, Folder 390)
    - Shackleford - Stewart (Box 36, Folder 391)
    - Shackleford - Stewart (Box 36, Folder 392)
    - Shackleford - Stewart (Box 36, Folder 393)
    - Troy, Robert P. - Weir, Wm. B. (Box 37, Folder 394)
    - Troy, Robert P. - Weir, Wm. B. (Box 37, Folder 395)
    - Troy, Robert P. - Weir, Wm. B. (Box 37, Folder 396)
    - Troy, Robert P. - Weir, Wm. B. (Box 37, Folder 397)
    - Troy, Robert P. - Weir, Wm. B. (Box 37, Folder 398)
    - Troy, Robert P. - Weir, Wm. B. (Box 37, Folder 399)
    - Troy, Robert P. - Weir, Wm. B. (Box 37, Folder 400)
    - Troy, Robert P. - Weir, Wm. B. (Box 37, Folder 401)
    - Troy, Robert P. - Weir, Wm. B. (Box 37, Folder 402)
    - Troy, Robert P. - Weir, Wm. B. (Box 37, Folder 403)
    - Troy, Robert P. - Weir, Wm. B. (Box 37, Folder 404)
    - Weiss, George - Wilcoxon, J.M. (Box 38, Folder 405)
    - Weiss, George - Wilcoxon, J.M. (Box 38, Folder 406)
    - Weiss, George - Wilcoxon, J.M. (Box 38, Folder 407)
    - Weiss, George - Wilcoxon, J.M. (Box 38, Folder 408)
    - Weiss, George - Wilcoxon, J.M. (Box 38, Folder 409)
    - Weiss, George - Wilcoxon, J.M. (Box 38, Folder 410)
    - Weiss, George - Wilcoxon, J.M. (Box 38, Folder 411)
    - Weiss, George - Wilcoxon, J.M. (Box 38, Folder 412)
    - Weiss, George - Wilcoxon, J.M. (Box 38, Folder 413)
    - Wilder, A.D. - Zollver, Henry (Box 39, Folder 414)
    - Wilder, A.D. - Zollver, Henry (Box 39, Folder 415)
    - Wilder, A.D. - Zollver, Henry (Box 39, Folder 416)
    - Wilder, A.D. - Zollver, Henry (Box 39, Folder 417)
    - Wilder, A.D. - Zollver, Henry (Box 39, Folder 418)
    - Wilder, A.D. - Zollver, Henry (Box 39, Folder 419)
    - Wilder, A.D. - Zollver, Henry (Box 39, Folder 420)
    - Wilder, A.D. - Zollver, Henry (Box 39, Folder 421)
    - Wilder, A.D. - Zollver, Henry (Box 39, Folder 422)
    - Ephemera (Box 40, Folder 423)
    - Ephemera (Box 40, Folder 424)
    - Ephemera (Box 40, Folder 425)
    - Ephemera (Box 40, Folder 426)
    - Ephemera (Box 40, Folder 427)
    - Ephemera (Box 40, Folder 428)
    - Ephemera (Box 40, Folder 429)
    - Ephemera (Box 40, Folder 430)
    - Ephemera (Box 40, Folder 431)
    - Related Correspondence from White's secretary R.W. GatesJune 1893 - June 5, 1897 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- Series 2. Legal and Political Papers
  - Briefs: Baldwin v. Durffee, p. 461 (Box 41)
  - Briefs: Ballerino v. Bigelow (Box 41)
    p. 72
  - Briefs: Bell v. Hollister (Box 41)
    p. 538
  - Briefs: Bell v. Stears (Box 41)
    p. 544
  - Briefs: Bixby v. Hadley (Box 41)
    pps. 530, 533
  - Briefs: Bixby v. Hansaker (Box 41)
    pps. 129, 441, 457
  - Briefs: Broderick, W. J. (Box 41)
    p. 327
  - Briefs: Brousseau v. Leonis (Box 41)
    p. 570
  - Briefs: Bull v. Strong (Box 41)
    p. 78
  - Briefs: Burdick v. Rolph (Box 41)
    p. 117
  - Briefs: Childs v. Ivers (Box 41)
    p. 211
  - Briefs: City v. Cohn (Box 41)
    p. 581
  - Briefs: Cleveland majorities (Box 41)
    p. 646
  - Briefs: Cochran, A.E. (Box 41)
    p. 458
  - Briefs: Colville v. Union Ice Co. (Box 41)
    p. 639
  - Briefs: Conant v. Heliman (Box 41)
    p. 579
  - Briefs: Connolly v. Wicks (Box 41)
    p. 580
  - Briefs: Coronel v. Wolfskill (Box 41)
    pps. 286, 287
  - Briefs: Downey and Eshelman (Box 41)
    p. 526
  - Briefs: Eaton, F. (Box 41)
    p. 148
  - Briefs: Estate of Abila (Box 41)
    p. 638
  - Briefs: Estate of Bolan (Box 41)
    pps. 512, 521, 687
  - Briefs: Estate of Childs (Box 41)
    pps. 163. 182, 184, 218, 233, 309, 311, 326, 438, 444, 462, 504, 522, 553, 557, 561, 683, 686, 689
  - Briefs: Estate of Cohn (Box 41)
    pps. 415, 467
  - Briefs: Estate of Dye (Box 41)
    p. 23
  - Briefs: Estate of Gamier (Box 41)
    pps. 432, 560, 568
  - Briefs: Estate of Leonis (Box 41)
    pps. 147, 149, 626, 629.
  - Briefs: Estate of Narvais (Box 41)
    pps. 333, 334, 434
  - Briefs: Estate of Estate of Newman (Box 41)
    p. 547
  - Briefs: Estate of Niemeyer (Box 41)
    pps. 424, 427
  - Briefs: Estate of Walker (Box 41)
    p. 492
  - Briefs: Extortion (Box 41)
    p. 165
  - Briefs: Field v. Shorb (Box 41)
    pps. 306, 445, 455
  - Briefs: Hutchinson, E. H. (Box 41)
    p. 465
  - Briefs: Jury list (Box 41)
    pps. 459, 472, 503
  - Briefs: Klauber v. Higgins (Box 41)
    pps. 186, 388
  - Briefs: La Sierra Water Co. (Box 41)
    p. 297
  - Briefs: Labory v. Los Angeles Orphan Asylum (Box 41)
    p. 94
  - Briefs: Los Angeles Farming and Milling Co. V. Hoff (Box 41)
    pps. 401, 429, 664
  - Briefs: Mesnager v. Hamilton (Box 41)
    pps. 282, 308
  - Briefs: Nosier v. Beale (Box 41)
    p. 565
  - Briefs: National Bank of California (Box 41)
    p. 162
  - Briefs: People v. Edelman (Box 41)
    p. 166
  - Briefs: People v. Hammond (Box 41)
    p. 669
  - Briefs: People v. Heliman (Box 41)
    p. 507
  - Briefs: People v. Samonset (Box 41)
    p. 474, 494
  - Briefs: Peterson v. Weder (Box 41)
    p. 647
  - Briefs: Ruiz v. Guiol (Box 41)
    p. 627
  - Briefs: Roberts v. Moore (Box 41)
    p. 33
  - Briefs: Sappenfield case (Box 41)
    p. 460
  - Briefs: Tuf free v. Polkemus (Box 41)
    p. 278
  - Briefs: Union Loan and Trust Co. v. So. Cal. R.R. (Box 41)
    p. 436
  - Briefs: United States v. Burt (Box 41)
    p. 9
  - Briefs: United States v. Caswell (Box 41)
    p. 606
  - Briefs: United States v. Trumbull (Box 41)
    p. 77
  - Briefs: Weeks v. Brockamp (Box 41)
    pps. 67, 132
  - Briefs: Wier v. Foord (Box 41)
    p. 40
  - Briefs: Wilgus v. Hearper Reynolds (Box 41)
    p. 614
  - Briefs: Antelope Valley Water Co. (Box 41)
    p. 266
  - Briefs: Archer v. Freeman (Box 41)
    p. 522
  - Briefs: Baldwin v. Durfee (Box 41)
    p. 330
  - Briefs: Bathgate v. Irvine (Box 41)
  - Briefs: Connolly v. Wicks (Box 41)
    p. 195
  - Briefs: Downey, J. G. (Box 41)
  - Briefs: Duncan v. Times Mirror Co. (Box 41)
    p. 407
  - Briefs: Estate of Broaded (Box 41)
    p. 172
  - Briefs: Estate of Childs (Box 41)
    pps. 15, 83, 91, 152, 307, 623, 626.
  - Briefs: Estate of Cohn (Box 41)
    pps. 123, 131, 136, 140, 153, 155, 159
  - Briefs: Estate of Downey (Box 41)
    pps. 308, 380, 402, 672
  - Briefs: Estate of Gamier (Box 41)
    p. 398
  - Briefs: Estate of Niemeyer (Box 41)
    p. 317
  - Briefs: Estate of Pratt (Box 41)
    pps. 373, 377, 382, 392
  - Briefs: Estate of Teahan (Box 41)
    p. 168
  - Briefs: Estate of Wilson (Box 41)
    pps. 440, 485, 534, 597
  - Briefs: Harvey v. Barker (Box 41)
    p. 269
  - Briefs: Harvey v. Meyer (Box 41)
    pps. 507, 529
  - Briefs: Kelly v. Harvey (Box 41)
    pps. 677, 684
  - Briefs: Klauber v. Higgins (Box 41)
    p. 682
  - Briefs: Leonard, Mary L. (Box 41)
    p. 160
  - Briefs: Los Angeles Farming and Milling Co. V. Thompson (Box 41)
    p. 415
  - Briefs: Naschinenfabrik v. Chino (Box 41)
    p. 629
  - Briefs: Meloy, William A. (Box 41)
    pps. 310, 315
  - Briefs: McFadden, J. (Box 41)
    p. 468
  - Briefs: Newmark, M. J. (Box 41)
    p. 419
  - Briefs: Olive Milling Land and Improvement Co. (Box 41)
    p. 369
  - Briefs: People v. Hammond (Box 41)
    p. 1
  - Briefs: People v. Jesurun (Box 41)
    p. 177
  - Briefs: Rhorer, George (Box 41)
    p. 379
  - Briefs: Union Ice Co. (Box 41)
  - Briefs: Union Loan and Trust Co. v. So. Cal. R.R. (Box 41)
    p. 635
  - Briefs: United States v. Harris (Box 41)
    p. 387
  - Briefs: Ventura Recorder (Box 41)
    p. 405
  - Briefs: Weir v. Vail (Box 41)
    p. 196
  - Briefs: White (Box 41)
  - Briefs: Wineburgh v. Pacific Coast S.S. Co. (Box 41)
    p. 477
  - Briefs: Baldwin v. Durfee (Box 41)
    pps. 116, 193
  - Briefs: Bell v. Hollister (Box 41)
    pps. 110, 326
  - Briefs: Bousseau v. Leonis (Box 41)
  - Briefs: Burke v. Workman (Box 41)
    p. 469
  - Briefs: Chase v. .Downey (Box 41)
    p. 170
  - Briefs: Childs, Emma S. (Box 41)
    pps. 330, 338
  - Briefs: Childs, Ruth E. (Box 41)
    p. 328
  - Briefs: City of Los Angeles v. Crystal Springs Water Company (Box 41)
    pps. 35, 47
  - Briefs: Connolly v. Wicks (Box 41)
    pps. 8, 18, 28, 32, 319, 471
  - Briefs: County v. Lankershi (Box 41)
    p. 54
  - Briefs: Doss v. Gibson (Box 41)
    p. 356
  - Briefs: Estate of Apablasa (Box 41)
    pps. 105, 115, 177, 178
  - Briefs: Estate of Bolan (Box 41)
    pps. 64, 208
  - Briefs: Estate of Childs (Box 41)
    pps. 144, 147, 150, 154, 156, 273
  - Briefs: Estate of Coleman (Box 41)
    p. 187
  - Briefs: Estate of Dye (Box 41)
    pps. 211, 221, 224
  - Briefs: Estate of Gamier (Box 41)
    pps. 155, 169
  - Briefs: Estate of Mailles (Box 41)
    pps. 158, 165, 174
  - Briefs: Estate of Maxey (Box 41)
    p. 161
  - Briefs: Estate of Meyberg (Box 41)
    pps. 218, 255
  - Briefs: Estate of Narvais (Box 41)
    pps. 44, 46, 196, 201, 203, 215, 228
  - Briefs: Estate of Niemeyer (Box 41)
    pps. 164, 175, 351
  - Briefs: Estate of Slack (Box 41)
    pps. 271, 275
  - Briefs: Estate of Teahan (Box 41)
    pps. 424, 440
  - Briefs: Estate of Wagner (Box 41)
    p. 258
  - Briefs: Ferguson v. City (Box 41)
    pps. 377, 404
  - Briefs: Field v. Shorb (Box 41)
    p. 34
  - Briefs: Forman v. Vandercook (Box 41)
    p. 376
  - Briefs: Gage v. Downey (Box 41)
    p. 243
  - Briefs: Hayne v. Gould (Box 41)
    pps. 279, 303
  - Briefs: Heinton, J.W. (Box 41)
    pps. 332, 335
  - Briefs: Journal v. Whitney (Box 41)
    p. 69
  - Briefs: Kilpatrick, et. al. (Box 41)
    p. 68
  - Briefs: Koebig v. Southern Pacific Co. (Box 41)
  - Briefs: Leonard v. Parker (Box 41)
    p. 246
  - Briefs: Los Angeles Farming and Milling Co. V. Hoff (Box 41)
  - Briefs: Lower California Matter (Box 41)
    p. 342
  - Briefs: Lytle Creek Water and Improvement Co. v. The Grapeland Irrigation District (Box 41)
    p. 190
  - Briefs: Milwaukee Furniture Co. v. Nightingale (Box 41)
    pps. 264, 445
  - Briefs: Ruiz v. Guiol (Box 41)
    p. 10
  - Briefs: San Pedro Lumber Co. v. Reynolds (Box 41)
    p. 179
  - Briefs: Sepulueda c. Bixby (Box 41)
    p. 444
  - Briefs: Thompson v. Hellman (Box 41)
    p. 403
  - Briefs: Tuf free v. Polkemus (Box 41)
    p. 214
  - Briefs: United States v. The Itata (Box 41)
    p. 207
  - Briefs: Werder v. Nelson (Box 41)
    p. 142
  - Briefs: White, Stephen N. (Box 41)
    p. 346
  - Briefs: Williams v. Fulton (Box 41)
    p. 449
  - Briefs: Wilson v. NcConnachic (Box 41)
    p. 298
  - Briefs: American Surety Co. of N.Y. (Box 42)
    p. 365
  - Briefs: Bathgate v. Irvine (Box 42)
  - Briefs: Brady v. Times Mirror Co. (Box 42)
    pps. 262, 268, 345, 421, 5 432.
  - Briefs: Childs (Box 42)
    pps. 173, 264
  - Briefs: Connolly v. Wicks (Box 42)
    p. 151
  - Briefs: Coronel v. Smith (Box 42)
    p. 645
  - Briefs: Crystal Springs Land and Water Co. V. City Of Los Angeles (Box 42)
    pps. 460, 475
  - Briefs: Davidson v. Calkins (Box 42)
    p. 582
  - Briefs: Downey v. Barker (Box 42)
    p. 312
  - Briefs: Estate of Connally (Box 42)
    pps. 463, 468, 473
  - Briefs: Estate of Downey (Box 42)
    pps. 65, 125, 133, 137, 140
  - Briefs: Estate of Estop (Box 42)
    p. 462
  - Briefs: Estate of Rumpp (Box 42)
    p. 585
  - Briefs: Estate of Sansinena (Box 42)
    pps. 267, 294, 327, 357,
  - Briefs: Fleming v. 'Consolidated Water Co. (Box 42)
    pps. 648, 654
  - Briefs: Fleming v. Lathrop (Box 42)
    p. 658
  - Briefs: Free Gold Mining Co. v. Spiers (Box 42)
    p. 452
  - Briefs: Kelly v. Harvey (Box 42)
  - Briefs: Karper v. Broderick (Box 42)
    p. 176
  - Briefs: Koebig V. Southern Pacific Co. (Box 42)
  - Briefs: Los Angeles Water Co. v. city of Los Angeles (Box 42)
    pps. 487, 500, 553, 568, 575, 580, 621, 625, 633, 688, 694, 701, 710
  - Briefs: Los Nietos and Ranchito Walnut G.A. (Box 42)
    p. 204
  - Briefs: Monroe, Charles, 360, 444, 456, 675 (Box 42)
    p. 131 5
  - Briefs: Morgan v. City Water Co. (Box 42)
    p. 710
  - Briefs: Patton v. Herald Publishing Co. (Box 42)
    p. 576
  - Briefs: People v. Alford (Box 42)
    p. 637
  - Briefs: People v. Shorb (Box 42)
    p. 280
  - Briefs: Robinson v. Times (Box 42)
  - Briefs: Smith-Coronel (Box 42)
  - Briefs: Smith v. Smith (Box 42)
    p. 709
  - Briefs: Spiliman V. City of Los Angeles (Box 42)
  - Briefs: Stracey v. City (Box 42)
    p. 710.
  - Briefs: Strong v. Los Nietos and Ranchito Walnut GA (Box 42)
    p. 556
  - Briefs: United States v. Hunter (Box 42)
    pps. 143, 478
  - Briefs: Voss (Box 42)
    p. 408
  - Briefs: Yndart V. Coronel (Box 42)
    p. 247
  - Bills Rendered, Instructions to Juries, Agreements (Box 42)
  - Memoranda of dates for trials, filing of motions. (Box 42)
  - Agreements and Instructions to Juries (Box 42)
  - Memoranda: dates for trials, 2 volumes (Box 42)
  - Memoranda: for Bills rendered (Box 42)
  - Alemaney - Bathgate, et. (Box 43)
  - Beal, E.F. - Hodge, E. (Box 44)
  - Hodge, Wm. W. - Millar, E.B. (Box 45)
  - Mitchell, H.M. - (Box 46)
    Folders 10-12 contain Ranulfo Pico Papers
  - Rumpp, W. - Standifer, W.R. (Box 47)
  - Stowell and Earl - Vail v. Weir (Box 48)
  - Weir v. Vail Bill Of Complaint (9th Circuit Ct.) (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Weir v. Vail Bill In Equity (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Weir v. Vail Bill Of Complaint (Super. Ct. L.A.) (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Weir v. Vail Plaintiff's Examination D. (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Weir v. Vail Transcript of Deed (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Weir v. Vail Deed (recorded in Book 45, #436, MaylO, 1876) (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Weir v. Vail Examination of William Shepard (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Weir v. Vail Plaintiff's demurrer (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Weir v. Vail Defendant's demurrer (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Weir v. Vail Plaintiff's Examination A (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Weir v. Vail Bill of Exceptions (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Weir v. Vail Vail's Direct Examination of by Hayes. (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Weir v. Vail Addtl. legal motions. (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Yellow Aster Mining and Milling Co. V. Winchell and Stanton. (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Yellow Aster Mining and Milling Co. V. Winchell and Stanton. (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Deeds (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Printed court documents: opinions, petitions. (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous legal papers. (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Financial, C,1888 - 1889 (Box 51)
  - Financial, D-G, 1888 - 1889; H - L, 18901880, 1888 - 1889 (Box 52)
  - Financial, M - S, 1890; D-E, 1892 - 18931890, 1892 - 1893 (Box 53)
- Series 3. Financial Papers
  - Bills, invoices, receipts and statements (Box 54)
  - 1889 - 1890 N thru 1891 - 1892 C1889 - 1892 (Box 54)
  - 1891 - 1892 D thru 1893 - 1894 D1891 - 1894 (Box 54)
  - 1893 - 1894 E thru Financial related (Box 54)
  - Check Stubs1892 - Mar. 1900 (Box 90)
- Series 4. Notebooks and Scrapbooks
  - Vol. VIIIDec. 1896 - June 1897
    Clippings dealing with law cases, politics and miscellaneous subjects
  - Vol. IX, Clippings dealing with law cases, politics and miscellaneous subjects
    Mar. 1897 - July 1897
  - Vol IA. Clippings on Miscellaneous Subjects (Folder 91)
  - Scrapbook Vol. I. Mar. 19, 1874 to Sept. 14, 1893 (Folder 91)
  - Vol. II1890 - 1892 (Folder 92)
    Mostly clippings on law cases
  - Vol. IIIDec. 1982 (Folder 93)
    Clippings from newspapers throughout Calif. dealing with White's candidacy for U.S. Senate.
  - Vol. IV1892 - 1894 (Folder 94)
    Clippings dealing with White's candidacy and election with miscellaneous political subjects.
  - Vol. V1894 - 1895 (Box 95)
    Clippings dealing with political and economic affairs.
  - Vol. VISept. 1894 - Feb. 1895 (Box 95)
    Clippings dealing with campaign activities of 1894.
  - Vol. VIIMar. 1896 - Oct. 1896 (Box 95)
    Controversy between White and Huntington over San Pedro National Democratic Convention at Chicago. White's campaign in Calif. for Bryan.
  - Notebook and scrapbook1873 - 1875, Bound (Box 96)
  - Vol. X1898 - 1899, 1881 - 1902 (Box 96)
    Largely clippings on political subjects, also on the water front cases and celebration upon the beginning of construction of the San Pedro breakwater. Scrapbook.
  - Vol. XI1900 (Box 96)
    Clippings dealing almost entirely with the National Democratic Convention
- Series 4. Miscellaneous
  - Unidentified Fragments (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - Letters not to White (Filed by subject) Miscellaneous. (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - Letters not to White (Filed by subject) Appointments and Patronage, Cannon, Marion (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - Letters not to White (Filed by subject) Armed Forces; Banking (Box 97, Folder 4)
    Perkins, George C. (1893 - 1923), senator
  - Letters not to White (Filed by subject) Consular Service, Harbor Matters and Indian Affairs (Box 97, Folder 5)
    Carbon copy of letter from Eureka Board of Harbor Commissioners to Gov. James H. Budd, concerning harbor defense against Spain, May 4, 1898.
  - Letters not to White (Filed by subject) Politics (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - Letters not to White (Filed by subject) Tariffs (Box 97, Folder 7)
    Including asphalt, express companies, insurance, ostrich feathers, opium, products of drugstores, raisins, sugar and wine.
  - Letters not to White (Filed by subject) U.S. Senate Business (Box 97, Folder 8)
    Bryan, William Jennings, 1860 - 1925; Griggs, John William, 1849 - 1927; Long, John D., 1838 - 1915; Olney, Warren, 1841 - 1921; Southwick, George, 1863 - 1912; Spaulding, Oliver Lyman, 1883 - 1922
  - Letters not to White (Filed by subject) U.S. Senate bills and miscellaneous papers (Box 97, Folder 9)
  - Legal Business Correspondence, A - B (Box 97, Folder 10)
  - Legal Business Correspondence, C - G (Box 97, Folder 11)
  - Legal Business Correspondence, H - M (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Legal Business Correspondence, N - V (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - Legal Business Correspondence, W. (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Legal Business Correspondence, Miscellaneous (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - Accounts (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - Legal Documents -General File (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - Legal Documents -General File (Box 98, Folder 7)
  - Affadavits (Box 98, Folder 8)
  - Circulars (Box 98, Folder 9)
  - Introductions (Box 98, Folder 10)
    Bennett, James Gordon, 1841 - 1918; Blain, James Gillespie, 1830 - 1893
  - Invitations (Box 98, Folder 11)
  - Speeches by Stephen White: reprints from the Congressional Record., one carbon typescript (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - Resolutions in honor of Stephen White. (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous printed leaflets and circulars. (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous printed leaflets and circulars. (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper clippings. (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - Lists. (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - Unsigned correspondence (incoming). (Box 99, Folder 7)
  - Cards:advertising, admission, and calling, Registry receipt, 1885; Western Union, credit card for Southern Pacific Co.; Pass to World's Columbian Exposition, 1893. (Box 99, Folder 8)
  - Photographs and printed illustrations. (Box 99, Folder 9)
  - Maps, building plans. (Box 99, Folder 10)